trafficbrokers.com 2011-12-06

# Traffic Brokers - The #1 Make Money Online Community

Privacy Policy  
We take your privacy very seriously, and we've created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. This page outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information.

If you want to opt-out of email communications from TrafficBrokers.com, cancel your account, or need to contact us for any other privacy related issue here's how to reach us:

1\. Email: [support@trafficbrokers.com](mailto:support@trafficbrokers.com?subject=&cc=&bcc=&body=)  
  
2\. Website: http://www.trafficbrokers.com/cancel.cgi  
  
3\. Postal Mail: 1675 Larimer Street, Suite 640, Denver, CO 80202  
  
4\. Telephone: (773)634-9931

| 

|   | 

|   | 

|   | 

---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**_What information does TrafficBrokers.com collect from visitors?_**

TrafficBrokers.com collects information from our visitors and users of our website and uses the information for marketing and administration purposes, in the fulfillment of our service commitment to you, or as required under the law.

As a user of this website, TrafficBrokers.com may collect your personally identifiable information when you visit our site and create a TrafficBrokers.com account.

The personally identifiable information that we collect is limited to just your name and email.

**_Why is information collected?_**

Information may be collected in an effort to enhance your user experience, provide you with information regarding TrafficBrokers.com services or other related special offers, and/or to provide you with the products and/or services that you request.

We, or our authorized affiliates, may also collect general information about transactions as they correspond to our advertisements or products. This aggregate information may include demographic and usage information, but 

_does not include personally identifiable information_.

This information is used in an aggregated manner to determine advertising effectiveness and is sometimes shared with our advertising partners for the same limited purpose.

**_How does TrafficBrokers.com protect my information?_**

We have implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personally identifiable information. Users' personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by certain key employees.

We do not collect or store any credit card or other financial information.

Should it be necessary to transmit your personally identifiable information to a reputable third party vendor to fulfill our service commitment to you, TrafficBrokers.com will require all recipients of such information to maintain the information as confidential information, use the information for the limited and intended purpose and agree not to disclose such information.

**_Will TrafficBrokers.com disclose the information it collects to others?_**

TrafficBrokers.com does not rent, sell or share any of the information collected by this site with unrelated 3rd-parties, except to provide the products or services you've purchased or requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in conjunction with illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TrafficBrokers.com's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;
  * We may share your user information with carefully selected and well-respected service providers or other companies that provide marketing services on our behalf or to other providers with whom we have joint marketing agreements;
  * We are required by law to provide the IRS with Tax ID numbers and/or other personally identifiable information about Affiliates who promote TrafficBrokers.com and earn over $600 in commissions in a calender year.  

**_Does TrafficBrokers.com use "cookies" or pixel "tags"?_**

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow website operators to better customize a site to your individual preferences.

The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and most major websites use them. We may use cookies to help provide you with a better experience on our site; however, we do not store personally identifying information in cookies.

Like many Web sites, TrafficBrokers.com may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement.

We may also implement pixel tags provided by other companies, and limit the collection of information for the same purpose. We do not store personally identifying information in pixels.

**_Can I access or modify the Personal Identifying Information collected?_**

You can view and/or modify the information provided to us at any time by logging in to your account, and clicking the "Account Info" link. You may also submit your request to modify your account information via any of the methods below.

**_What if I want to Opt-Out of email communications from TrafficBrokers.com?_**

TrafficBrokers.com provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future promotional communications from us. You may do so in the following ways.

Please note however that even if you opt-out, you may still receive important announcements or updates regarding your TrafficBrokers.com account unless you cancel your account.

1\. Email: [support@trafficbrokers.com](mailto:support@trafficbrokers.com?subject=&cc=&bcc=&body=)  
  
2\. Website: http://www.trafficbrokers.com/cancel.cgi  
  
3\. Postal Mail: 1675 Larimer Street, Suite 640, Denver, CO 80202  
  
4\. Telephone: (773)634-9931

**_Can children or minors use TrafficBrokers.com?_**

TrafficBrokers.com does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from or about anyone under the age of 18. If we discover we have received such information in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

If you believe TrafficBrokers.com has any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please contact us. If you are under 18, you may use TrafficBrokers.com only under the supervision of a parent or guardian.

**_Links to Other Sites_**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that TrafficBrokers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**_Your consent_**

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide per this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy.

Should this be necessary, we will post any changes here so you're always aware of the information we collect and how we use it.

**_Contacting TrafficBrokers.com_**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy-related practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via one of the methods above.

This Privacy Policy was last updated October 23rd, 2010.
